Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Moving images and audio recordings
  - Audio cassettes
    - Unique
      - Zulu Nation Web Site, Floppy disk: 3 1/2 inch (Box Box 145)
      - Zulu Nation Web Site, Floppy disk: 3 1/2 inch (Box Box 145)
      - Zulu Nation Web Site, Floppy disk: 3 1/2 inch (Box Box 145)
      - Zulu Nations Hip Hop anniversary of Germany with Afrika Bambaataa [inside "Wu-tang Mastermix"], audiocassette (Box Box 145)
      - Box of floppy discs (Box Box 145)
      - Grey box of tapes, Audiocassettes | DATs (Box Box 143)